[{"answer": "Good.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "How does it feel to be back?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Does it?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Are you still proud of CNN?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "I watch it, you bet.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Do you still watch CNN?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "I like most of what I see.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Do you like what you see?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "I'd have to really give it a lot of thought and a lot of study, which I have not done, because nobody has asked me to do it.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "If you had the competition that's around now in cable when you first started, in other words, if there had been a FOX News with right-wing star anchors, MSNBC had Rachel Maddow and the others, would you do anything differently?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "But do you think that CNN should remain the impartial observer of news?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "I think it's terrible that politics have gotten so money oriented with this Supreme Court ruling that the corporations can give unlimited amounts, that the moneyed interests are taking over the country.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "What do you think of your country?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "I like him.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "How is he doing?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Well, I would have liked to see him be -- his positions are good on the environment, but he put health care ahead of the energy bill.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Where do you think he's not been strong enough?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "I think -- I think war should be avoided at all costs.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Is that really what America should have done, rather than going in with men on the ground, big, large phalanxes of troops, actually say we're going to tackle the terrorists through intelligence, through Special Forces and so on?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I believe in total nuclear disarmament.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "What would you do about Iran if you were the American president?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "I feel good.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "What do you feel, Ted, when you see that like clip again?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "I wanted to better inform the world.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "What did you really want to achieve with CNN?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Do you feel that you succeeded?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Over 100.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "How many?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Was that the story, the event that made you realize just how big CNN could become?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "I -- you know, just all we did was televise what we saw.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "What do you think the difference that decision, that capability made to the way the war was covered?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "But did it bring a greater truth, do you think, to war coverage, the fact that you were there?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Well, it shook us up.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Your third story that you singled out, 9/11, the CNN coverage of that, what did that do to America, that moment?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "Probably.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "Ted, Jane Fonda, was she the great love of your life?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Have you ever quite got over her?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "Do you think you ever will?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "You want me to rank them?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "They all broke my heart.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Which upset you the most?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "I'm a more experienced man, because those -- you know, the AOL merger and the subsequent -- basically destruction of my wealth, they hurt at the time, but I just toughed it out.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Are you a better man for having experienced loss?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "It felt -- it felt bad.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "What does that feel like?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "It really hurt, because we were making our budget and I was loyal to the management of the company.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "How does that feel?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "With great difficulty.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Well, most men watching this will be going, come on, Ted, how did you get away with that?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "URNER: Some of them are.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Are they good friends with each other?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "A little bit.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Did you try and win her back?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Twice.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Sort of.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "But there's a difference between being in love and loving?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "I think what we need is for humanity to be great.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "What should America be doing now to revive itself?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "I'm working so hard on the environment and nuclear weapons and the survival issues that the financial -- the financial issues and a lot of other areas, you can't be an expert on everything.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "What do you think of the concept of moral capitalism?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "But does it help America and its national interests if very successful American companies that create their ideas here, then shift out much of the production jobs to other countries?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Having some, you've got to have enough to eat.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Has money made you happy, happier than you would have been without money?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "No, I could have had three.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "So five is the optimum number?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "On -- my doctors said I was allergic to potatoes, so I couldn't --", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "You've given up?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "URNER: Yes.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Any alcohol?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Tobacco?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Hard drugs?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "I can't even drink a Coca-Cola, you know, no soft drinks.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "What are you allowed to do?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "I'm -- water.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "What are you existing on?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Who's going to win, do you think?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "I'd like to say that right now, in the last few years, the Democrats have been closer -- have been more pro-environment.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "Are you more Republican or Democrat these days?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "I -- a lot of the things that he did I didn't agree with.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "What was your overview of his tenure?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "The greatest single thing is to see my children all turn out well, all five of them.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "All the things that you've experienced, what's been the greatest moment of your life?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "URNER: They have.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "And have they?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "My proudest personal achievement.", "docId": "120528pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Is that your proudest achievement?", "qSentId": 538}]